In the given class of the binary search tree, implemented using dynamic memory representation, implement a recursive method which is calculating the depth of the tree level which has the most nodes (please mind the efficency of the method). Recursive method with proper arguments should be added to the class of the binary tree. Check the method for different use cases calling from the main method.
